fantrax.com 2013-10-31

# Privacy Policy - Fantrax

**OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**

This Privacy Policy applies to the www.fantrax.com website owned and operated by Septillium LLC. (hereinafter referred to as "Fantrax", "we", "our", or "us"). The Fantrax website is an interactive fantasy sports website which allows users to access sports-related information, software, merchandise and services. Fantrax respects the privacy of its users and is committed to protecting the personal information which it collects. This Fantrax Privacy Policy has been prepared to assist you in understanding the type of personal information that we may collect, how it used and with whom it may be shared. It also explains how your personal information is protected, and how it may be accessed. Our Policy is modeled after the Canadian Standards Association Model Code for the Protection of Personal Information and has been developed to comply with the federal Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act. We recommend that you review this Privacy Policy carefully and to check back periodically as the Policy may be amended from time to time. 

**COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

"Personal information" is personally identifiable information such as your name, address, e-mail address, gender, birth date, password, and includes information about your product and service subscriptions and usage, credit information and billing records, service and recorded complaints. 

Personal information is collected by Fantrax only when you specifically and knowingly choose to provide it to us, such as when you register for a league, enter a Fantrax contest/promotion, request our electronic communications, communicate with us via telephone, mail, email or "contact us" tool, participate in on-line chat room or bulletin boards or choose to subscribe to receive information, products or services from Fantrax. 

We may also receive personal information from our business partners and other third parties, provided that such third parties confirm to us that they have obtained your consent to the disclosure of your personal information. 

Personal information does not include certain business information, such as employee's job title, business address, e-mail address or work telephone number. 

"Non-personal" information is information of an anonymous nature. Non-personal information may include your Internal Protocol Address (IP Address) or aggregate information, such as the number of visitors to the website or their geographic location. Non-personal information is collected by Fantrax through its website and may be used for technical, research and analytical purposes. Non-personal information collected through surveys, existing files and public archives may be used by the Fantrax to analyze its markets or to develop or enhance service offerings. 

**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Fantrax uses your personal information primarily for the purpose of providing you with the products and services you have requested from us, such as customizing the content you view, receiving newsletters and/or other communications for which you have registered, special offers or promotional materials, or confirming or fulfilling an order you have made. 

Your personal information is used to communicate with you about your account and to provide you with information related to other Fantrax services. We may use your personal information from time to time to inform you about changes or enhancements to our products and services. We retain your website user ID and password so that upon request by you and receipt of identification we may remind you of them. 

If you indicated that you were interested in receiving offers or information from selected Fantrax sponsors or advertisers, your personal information may also be used to contact you or to send you e-mail materials and other mailings about products and services that might be of interest to you. You always have the option, however, to advise us not to share your personal information with other Fantrax partners or to exclude you from marketing offers for other products or services. 

If you enter a contest or other promotion offered by a Fantrax, your personal information will be used to administer the promotion, including the use of your name and selected other information for the purposes of contacting, announcing and promoting the winner(s) of the promotion. 

Fantrax may also contact you from time to time to conduct market research and surveys in an effort to continually improve our product and service offerings. 

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Unless you specifically authorize us to release your personal information, Fantrax will not sell, lease or trade your personal information to other third parties, unless required or permitted by law. 

To enable us to more efficiently provide the products and services you have requested from us, Fantrax may share your personal information with selected third parties who perform services for us or supply goods. Such third parties may perform processing and other specialized services, such as prize fulfillment of our contests, collection of overdue accounts, product delivery or credit card processing. All third party service providers are provided only with such information as is necessary in the circumstances. Information provided to third parties may be used only for the purpose stipulated by us and is subject to strict terms of confidentiality. 

**CONSENT**

When you voluntarily provide us with your personal information, we assume you consent to its collection, use and disclosure in accordance with the Fantrax Privacy Policy and as described at the time of collection. In some cases, we may expressly request your consent to the collection, use or disclosure or your personal information or provide you with an opportunity to opt out of certain uses or disclosures of your personal information. We will seek your prior consent to the collection, use and disclosure of the information as required by applicable privacy legislation. 

If our intended use or disclosure of personal information changes, we will notify you accordingly. Subject to legal and contractual requirements, you can refuse to consent to our collection, use or disclosure of information about you. You may also withdraw your consent to any further collection, use or disclosure of information about you at any time by giving us reasonable notice and subject to contractual and legal restrictions. If you choose to opt-out of any use of your personal information, we keep your contact information so that your request can honoured. 

Your personal information will not be used for any other purpose without your consent, except for limited circumstances where permitted or required by law, such as to collect a debt that you may owe to us or to comply with a court order or government regulations. 

**USE OF COOKIES**

Fantrax uses a browser feature called a "cookie" to collect information anonymously and track user patterns on the Fantrax website. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a website. "Cookies" contain a unique identification number that identifies your browser, but not you, to our computers each time you visit one of our websites. Cookies tell us which pages of our websites are visited and by how many people. We use cookies to better understand how you use our website and to improve the performance of our website. 

The use of cookies is an industry standard and many major browsers are initially set up to accept them. If you do not want to allow information to be collected through the use of cookies, you can generally opt out of providing such information by resetting your browser to reject cookies or obtain notification when you have received a cookie. However, if you disable the use of cookies, you may not be able to use some of the features available on our website. 

**ACCURACY**

Fantrax will try to ensure that information about you is accurate, complete and up-to-date. However, please inform Fantrax to whom you provided your information of any change of name, address or other information. In the event you have questions about the accuracy of factual information we have collected about you, you will have access to that information in order to verify and update it. If we have disclosed inaccurate information about you to a third party, we will be pleased to contact the third party in order to correct the information. 

**SECURITY**

Fantrax is committed to taking all reasonable precautions to safeguard the privacy of personal information which has been provided by its users. We use technical, contractual, administrative and physical security steps to protect your personal information. Security measures such as locked cabinets, restricted access and the use of passwords and encryption have been adopted to protect your personal information against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. Our employees have been trained to respect your privacy at all times and those employees with access to your personal information shall use your personal information strictly in accordance with the Fantrax Privacy Policy. We will protect your credit card information by using industry standard encryption technology. 

Please be aware that no data transmission over the Internet or via e-mail is completely secure and therefore we cannot guarantee protection of all personal information in all cases. For example, we cannot guarantee protection against interception, misappropriation, misuse, or alteration, or that your information will not be disclosed or accessed by the unauthorized acts of others. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. If you provide us with your credit card number, you should not send it electronically unless the email is encrypted or your browser indicates that the access to our website is secure. Materials posted to online forums such as bulletin boards or chat rooms are public, not secure, and may be viewed by anyone. Any personal information you post may be collected and used by anyone and may result in unsolicited messages from other parties. 

**WEBSITE LINKS**

The Fantrax Site may contain links to external websites. These are provided for your convenience only. We do not have control over the content or privacy and security practices and policies of third party sites, and cannot be head liable for the actions of those third parties who maintain such websites. Any personal information you provide on linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy. We recommend that you review the privacy and security practices and policies of external websites before providing them with your personal information. 

**ACCESS AND CONTACTING US**

If you have any questions, comments or complaints about the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information by Fantrax, or if you simply want to know whether we have any of your personal information on file, you may contact Fantrax's Privacy Officer at: [privacy@fantrax.com](mailto:privacy@fantrax.com) or write us at: 

2400 Oxford Drive  
Suite 450  
Bethel Park, PA   15102  
USA

Except in limited circumstances, as specifically provided by applicable privacy legislation, Fantrax can tell you whether it holds personal information about you. We can inform you of the source of your personal information, allow you to access to your personal information, find out how it has been used and the third parties to whom it has been disclosed. We also provide you with the means to access, correct, update, change or delete any personal information you may have provided to us. 

Fantrax will only refuse access to information about you in those limited circumstances permitted or required by applicable privacy legislation. If Fantrax refuses access to you, it will provide you with the reasons for its refusal upon request. Exceptions may include information that contains references to other individuals, information that cannot be disclosed for legal, security or commercial proprietary reasons, and information that is subject to solicitor-client or litigation privilege. Fantrax will respond to your requests for access in accordance with applicable privacy legislation.
